<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Team AUV-IITK</title>
    <link>http://example.org/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Team AUV-IITK</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 18:04:33 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>ANSYS helps AUV-IITK design its latest vehicle Anahita</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/2019-05-06-ansys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 18:04:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/2019-05-06-ansys/</guid>
      <description>AUV-IITK is a multidisciplinary team of IITK students involved in designing, manufacturing, and testing of a series of Autonomous Underwater Vehicles (AUVs), working towards providing a research platform for geoscientific research while preparing to compete in prestigious competitions such as NIOT, SAUVC, and RoboSub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Useful Tips for ROS Users</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/2017-11-07-ros-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 21:04:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/2017-11-07-ros-tips/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Earlier people had to write a large amount of code ranging from low-level driver functions to high-level control algorithms for their robots. I too experienced this &lt;em&gt;pain&lt;/em&gt; when I started working on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://auviitk.com&#34;&gt;underwater vehicle&lt;/a&gt; project in my undergraduate university. This approach sometimes made changing even one sensor&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to AUVeScope</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/2017-10-17-welcome-to-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 20:04:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/2017-10-17-welcome-to-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Really Need An i7</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/2016-03-31-do-you-really-need-an-i7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 04:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/2016-03-31-do-you-really-need-an-i7/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;when-raspberry-pi-2-and-odroid-u3-fail-you-what-next-back-to-x64&#34;&gt;When Raspberry Pi 2 and Odroid U3 fail you. What next? Back to x64.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  Initially Shikher thought that buying a low power armh processor was a very wise choice. Low power meant lower battery consumption so lighter batteries. Also single chip armh processors like Raspberry Pi and Odroid are way cheaper. The world was good. Until one day OpenCV came along. Initially he seemed like a nice guy. Resourceful. With his awesome HighGUI and shiny high power tools like HoughCircle, Contrast stretching he seemed like a guy Shikher&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>